[{"show": "q", "color": "color2", "question": "who took over supervising the investigation after Attorney General Eric Holder recused himself", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "Deputy Attorney General James Cole", "id": 1},{"show": "q", "color": "color0", "question": "Cole wrote to Gary B. Pruitt", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "\"The subpoenas were limited to a reasonable period of time and did not seek the content of any calls\"", "id": 2},{"show": "q", "color": "color4", "question": "Under Holder, the Justice Department has prosecuted more government officials for alleged leaks under [] than all his predecessors combined. ", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "the World War I-era Espionage Act", "id": 3},{"show": "q", "color": "color1", "question": "The Obama administration has brought indictments against[]  for leaking information.", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "five government workers", "id": 4},{"show": "q", "color": "color2", "question": "[] is pursuing a sixth case against Bradley Manning,", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "The Defense Department ", "id": 5},{"show": "q", "color": "color1", "question": "Senate Majority Leader Harry Reid, a [], told reporters today the subpoena of the AP records was \u201cinexcusable and there\u2019s no way to justify this.\u201d", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "Nevada Democrat", "id": 6},{"show": "q", "color": "color3", "question": "Holder, who has been targeted by Republicans over the probe, said at a news conference in Washington today that he recused himself", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "\u201cto avoid the appearance of a potential conflict of interest and to make sure that the investigation was seen as independent.\u201d", "id": 7},{"show": "q", "color": "color0", "question": "Cole, in his letter to the AP, said the investigation into national security leaks included more than", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "550 interviews and the review of tens of thousands of documents before the Justice Department sought the AP records.", "id": 8},{"show": "q", "color": "color0", "question": "Cole said the subpoenas were part of the criminal investigation opened in ", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "May 2012.", "id": 9},{"show": "q", "color": "color2", "question": " The Justice Department subpoenaed records from \u201ca portion\u201d of the months of ", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "April and May 2012.", "id": 10},{"show": "q", "color": "color3", "question": "To contact the reporters on this story", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "Phil Mattingly in Washington at pmattingly@bloomberg.net; Jim Snyder in Washington at jsnyder24@bloomberg.net", "id": 11},{"show": "q", "color": "color1", "question": "To contact the editor responsible for this story", "difficulty": 5, "answer": "Steven Komarow at skomarow1@bloomberg.net", "id": 12}]